## Natallie Barreto

Personal Information

Address: 10113 Eastmar

Commons Blvd, APT 1331 Orlando

FL, 32825

Phone:

(407)-259-9964

Email:

Nat.barreto@icloud.com

**Dob:** APR 13, 1998

Languages

Spanish (fluent)

English (fluent)

Skills

- -fast learner
- -Team player
- -Over the line customer service
- -Bilingual
- -Problem solver

Summary:

Motivated team player committed to bringing success to the company with what I have to offer. I am currently enrolled in school and have experience in working in a financial institution. I am a fast learner striving to not only achieve my personal goals but to also help everyone in the team with whatever I can.

## Experience

Addition Financial (2018-Current)

**Teller**: Sales, Customer service, heavy cash handling, processing checks, printing money orders and checks, closing accounts, PC/ Microsoft skills

**Universal Agent** (2019): Customer service, Sales oriented, opening accounts, wire transfers, taking loan applications, helping members with all member needs, Online banking assistance and processing financial transactions.

Publix: clerk (2016-2018):

Customers service, fast pace environment, time management, positive attitude, money handling.

## Education

Valencia College/UCF

2018-Current

**Orange Technical College** 

2015

**University High School**